[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 27, "question": "Jesse, how are you?", "question_tokens": ["Jesse", ",", "how", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 28, "answer": "I'm doing well, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "doing", "well", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 29, "question": "How re you?", "question_tokens": ["How", "re", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "NN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 30, "answer": "You are looking very well.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "are", "looking", "very", "well", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "POS", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 85, "question": "Is that right?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 86, "answer": "Yes, that's true.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "that", "'s", "true", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 109, "question": "How does that work?", "question_tokens": ["How", "does", "that", "work", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 110, "answer": "I will.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "will", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 130, "question": "You're basically endorsing a form of fascism, aren't you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "basically", "endorsing", "a", "form", "of", "fascism", ",", "are", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 131, "answer": "We're already fascists, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "'re", "already", "fascists", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ":", "RB", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 146, "question": "Why is it just one way?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "is", "it", "just", "one", "way", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "CD", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 147, "answer": "Well, I guess that -- here's what I thought when I read your book.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "guess", "that", "--", "here", "'s", "what", "I", "thought", "when", "I", "read", "your", "book", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NNPS", "CC", "NNPS", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 152, "question": "How do you actually have a government that works if everyone is an independent?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "actually", "have", "a", "government", "that", "works", "if", "everyone", "is", "an", "independent", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 153, "answer": "Well, you can still -- you can turn the Democrats and Republicans into special interests, which is what they are anyway.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "can", "still", "--", "you", "can", "turn", "the", "Democrats", "and", "Republicans", "into", "special", "interests", ",", "which", "is", "what", "they", "are", "anyway", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 161, "question": "These would be independents formerly known as Democrats and Republicans, wouldn't they?", "question_tokens": ["These", "would", "be", "independents", "formerly", "known", "as", "Democrats", "and", "Republicans", ",", "would", "n't", "they", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "MD", "VB", "NNS", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NNPS", "CC", "NNPS", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 162, "answer": "No, not necessarily.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "not", "necessarily", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 168, "question": "You know why?", "question_tokens": ["You", "know", "why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "."], "aSentId": 169, "answer": "Go on.", "answer_tokens": ["Go", "on", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 170, "question": "You know why?", "question_tokens": ["You", "know", "why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "."], "aSentId": 171, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 198, "question": "When you hear the president and Republican nominee going at it like this, given the state of economy, what's your reaction?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "hear", "the", "president", "and", "Republican", "nominee", "going", "at", "it", "like", "this", ",", "given", "the", "state", "of", "economy", ",", "what", "'s", "your", "reaction", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NNP", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 199, "answer": "Well, my reaction, it doesn't matter.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "my", "reaction", ",", "it", "does", "n't", "matter", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 236, "question": "What do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 237, "answer": "I think it's awful.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "'s", "awful", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 257, "question": "So presumably you'll be boycotting FOX and MSNBC on your book tour, will you, Jesse?", "question_tokens": ["So", "presumably", "you", "'ll", "be", "boycotting", "FOX", "and", "MSNBC", "on", "your", "book", "tour", ",", "will", "you", ",", "Jesse", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 258, "answer": "I won't be boycotting them.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "wo", "n't", "be", "boycotting", "them", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jesse"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 264, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 265, "answer": "-- will have me on.", "answer_tokens": ["--", "will", "have", "me", "on", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "PRP", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 323, "question": "He has?", "question_tokens": ["He", "has", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 324, "answer": "Well, he is pulling them out.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "he", "is", "pulling", "them", "out", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 326, "question": "He's pulling them out, isn't he?", "question_tokens": ["He", "'s", "pulling", "them", "out", ",", "is", "n't", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "PRP", "RP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 327, "answer": "Well, I guess he is.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "guess", "he", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 341, "question": "What would you do with Iran?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "you", "do", "with", "Iran", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 342, "answer": "Well, I'll give you a scenario.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'ll", "give", "you", "a", "scenario", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Iran"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ":"], "qSentId": 365, "question": "So the U.S. -- the U.S. is definitely threatened by these countries in what way?", "question_tokens": ["So", "the", "U.S.", "--", "the", "U.S.", "is", "definitely", "threatened", "by", "these", "countries", "in", "what", "way", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NNP", ":", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "WP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 366, "answer": "You don't think --", "answer_tokens": ["You", "do", "n't", "think", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["U.S.", "U.S."]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 424, "question": "You mean \"Dallas,\" not the royal wedding?", "question_tokens": ["You", "mean", "``", "Dallas", ",", "''", "not", "the", "royal", "wedding", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "``", "NNP", ",", "''", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 425, "answer": "Actually both were.", "answer_tokens": ["Actually", "both", "were", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Dallas"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJR", "."], "qSentId": 442, "question": "Was it all you hoped it would be when you signed up for this?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "it", "all", "you", "hoped", "it", "would", "be", "when", "you", "signed", "up", "for", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 443, "answer": "More.", "answer_tokens": ["More", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 444, "question": "Really, why?", "question_tokens": ["Really", ",", "why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "WRB", "."], "aSentId": 445, "answer": "We had this realization we would never work together again.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "had", "this", "realization", "we", "would", "never", "work", "together", "again", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 460, "question": "What?", "question_tokens": ["What", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "."], "aSentId": 461, "answer": "I mean, you look so nice and normal today.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "you", "look", "so", "nice", "and", "normal", "today", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 474, "question": "Were you remotely concerned, given that you were the top dog, if you like, that it might damage the brand?", "question_tokens": ["Were", "you", "remotely", "concerned", ",", "given", "that", "you", "were", "the", "top", "dog", ",", "if", "you", "like", ",", "that", "it", "might", "damage", "the", "brand", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", ",", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 475, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "WRB", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 476, "question": "How long did you think about it?", "question_tokens": ["How", "long", "did", "you", "think", "about", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 477, "answer": "About until they told me how much I was going to make.", "answer_tokens": ["About", "until", "they", "told", "me", "how", "much", "I", "was", "going", "to", "make", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 478, "question": "How much was it?", "question_tokens": ["How", "much", "was", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 479, "answer": "I don't remember.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "remember", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 487, "question": "How much did the friendship come into it?", "question_tokens": ["How", "much", "did", "the", "friendship", "come", "into", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 488, "answer": "Well, I wouldn't be doing it without them.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "would", "n't", "be", "doing", "it", "without", "them", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "RB", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 507, "question": "Is everything OK, back to normal?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "everything", "OK", ",", "back", "to", "normal", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "VBG", "NNP", ",", "RB", "TO", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 508, "answer": "So far, yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["So", "far", ",", "yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Germany"]}, "docId": "120616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 514, "question": "Was that your chuckle or was it one you perfected?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "that", "your", "chuckle", "or", "was", "it", "one", "you", "perfected", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "CD", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 515, "answer": "AGMAN: In Germany, it's not my chuckle.", "answer_tokens": ["AGMAN", ":", "In", "Germany", ",", "it", "'s", "not", "my", "chuckle", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 532, "question": "Did you really say that?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "really", "say", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 533, "answer": "He said that.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "said", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 537, "question": "You think that's evil?", "question_tokens": ["You", "think", "that", "'s", "evil", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 538, "answer": "No wonder I drank.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "wonder", "I", "drank", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 540, "question": "Did you like being, for what you were for a long time, the most evil man on television?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "like", "being", ",", "for", "what", "you", "were", "for", "a", "long", "time", ",", "the", "most", "evil", "man", "on", "television", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", ",", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 541, "answer": "Well, you know, I don't think I was an evil man.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "I", "was", "an", "evil", "man", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 548, "question": "That is evil, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["That", "is", "evil", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 549, "answer": "Especially against his own family.", "answer_tokens": ["Especially", "against", "his", "own", "family", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 551, "question": "Did you like the reputation?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "like", "the", "reputation", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 552, "answer": "Of course I do, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Of", "course", "I", "do", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["J.R."]}, "docId": "120616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "WP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 554, "question": "How do people react even now?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "people", "react", "even", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "NNS", "VB", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 555, "answer": "They -- the question they say is who shot J.R.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "--", "the", "question", "they", "say", "is", "who", "shot", "J.R", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 556, "question": "You ever tell them?", "question_tokens": ["You", "ever", "tell", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 557, "answer": "Yes, yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bing Crosby"]}, "docId": "120616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 558, "question": "What did you say?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "say", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 559, "answer": "Bing Crosby's daughter.", "answer_tokens": ["Bing", "Crosby", "'s", "daughter", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 566, "question": "When you guys are filming in Dallas, presuming you live there for the duration, when you walk around, it must be like the royal family, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "guys", "are", "filming", "in", "Dallas", ",", "presuming", "you", "live", "there", "for", "the", "duration", ",", "when", "you", "walk", "around", ",", "it", "must", "be", "like", "the", "royal", "family", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBG", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 567, "answer": "Everywhere.", "answer_tokens": ["Everywhere", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Dallas"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["U.K."]}, "docId": "120616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 570, "question": "Where are you most popular outside America?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "are", "you", "most", "popular", "outside", "America", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "JJS", "JJ", "NN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 571, "answer": "I think it was in the U.K.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "was", "in", "the", "U.K", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 575, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 576, "answer": "Every night, yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Every", "night", ",", "yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 615, "question": "How do you feel about it?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "feel", "about", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 616, "answer": "Well, I actually was completely excited about what I considered to be a fun challenge.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "actually", "was", "completely", "excited", "about", "what", "I", "considered", "to", "be", "a", "fun", "challenge", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["John Ross"]}, "docId": "120616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 619, "question": "Is he everything like his father or nothing like his father?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "he", "everything", "like", "his", "father", "or", "nothing", "like", "his", "father", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 620, "answer": "John Ross was a little baby.", "answer_tokens": ["John", "Ross", "was", "a", "little", "baby", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 627, "question": "Am I right?", "question_tokens": ["Am", "I", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 628, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 638, "question": "How have you found it coming into this iconic show?", "question_tokens": ["How", "have", "you", "found", "it", "coming", "into", "this", "iconic", "show", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 639, "answer": "It's been wonderful.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "been", "wonderful", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["1980"]}, "docId": "120616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 644, "question": "How old were you when \"Dallas\" -- how old are you, if you don't mind me asking?", "question_tokens": ["How", "old", "were", "you", "when", "``", "Dallas", "''", "--", "how", "old", "are", "you", ",", "if", "you", "do", "n't", "mind", "me", "asking", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBD", "PRP", "WRB", "``", "NNP", "''", ":", "WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 645, "answer": "I was born in 1980.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "born", "in", "1980", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Dallas"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 657, "question": "Jesse, for you, from \"Desperate House Wives\" to \"Dallas,\" does it get any better?", "question_tokens": ["Jesse", ",", "for", "you", ",", "from", "``", "Desperate", "House", "Wives", "''", "to", "``", "Dallas", ",", "''", "does", "it", "get", "any", "better", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "TO", "``", "NNP", ",", "''", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJR", "."], "aSentId": 658, "answer": "You know, I feel incredibly blessed to have the opportunity to be another television phenomenon.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "feel", "incredibly", "blessed", "to", "have", "the", "opportunity", "to", "be", "another", "television", "phenomenon", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Dallas"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120616pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 682, "question": "Can we have a little critique?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "we", "have", "a", "little", "critique", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 683, "answer": "They're going to drag us into another 13 years.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "'re", "going", "to", "drag", "us", "into", "another", "13", "years", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]